(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 1,
"subtitles": 2
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
It was music that brought me to this country.
In the undulating whirlwind of life,
it's only normal to seek some place you belong.
...and that place you belong is often underscored by...
...a thing that you like.
A thing that draws you in and gives you an identity.
But I had obligations. Ya know, stuff to do.
Stuff I HAD to do.
It's funny how liking one thing can lead to loving another thing.
That was the case with me, actually.
Walking around, confused, bored...
Lost, I guess.
And then, just like that- there's a moment where...
...it clicks.
It clicks, and suddenly, you're different.
Different in some way you can't explain.
Huh?
Oh! Where are you...?
A rabbit hole appears before you.
And you see how far it takes you.
よふかしのうた
Call of the Night
Lyrics: R-指定 Music: DJ松永
Lyrics: R-Shitei Music: DJ Matsunaga
よふかしのうた
Call of the Night
照らしてって moonlight
Illuminate me, moonlight
目を奪って ブルーライト
Captivate my eyes, blue light
ネオンサインが呼ぶ 表裏
The neon signs are calling, inside out
よふかしのうた
Call of the Night
連れ去って midnight
Take me away, midnight
血走った red eyes
With bloodshot red eyes
大人たちの 子守唄
A lullaby for adults
なんせ俺たちの夜は忙しい
Because our nights are so busy
keep on dancing さあ鬼の居ぬ間に
Keep on dancing while the devil's away
俺たちの夜は忙しい oh yeah
Our nights are so busy, oh yeah
Yeah
なんせ俺たちの夜は忙しい
Because our nights are so busy
keep on dancing さあ鬼の居ぬ間に
Keep on dancing while the devil's away
俺たちの夜は忙しい oh yeah
Our nights are so busy, oh yeah
Yeah
ガキの頃から夜が好きだった
I've loved the night since I was a kid
9時に寝るのはなんか嫌だった
I hated having to sleep at 9 o'clock
なんとなくただ勿体なかった
It somehow felt like a total waste
甘いこと案外知りたかった
I actually wanted to know the sweet secrets
エーイ いわゆる散漫なトーク
Hey, call it scatterbrained small talk
投げ売りテレビみたいなサマートーク
Like summer talk on a bargain bin TV
広く もっと深く
Wider, and even deeper
12 o'clock から五月雨時まで
From 12 o'clock 'til the early summer rain
初めてお前を跨いだのは
The first time I straddled you
いや 初めて跨がったのは確か14
No, the first time I got on was surely at 14
俺は何も知らぬわらべ
I was just a child who knew nothing
とりあえず全てが新しい
For now, everything is so new
注がれた形にその香り
Into the poured shape and its scent
雫先に合うその黒い肌に
Into that black skin that meets the droplets
吸い込まれてった
I was sucked right in
手招きされるままに
Just as I was beckoned
それからお前は音楽を教え
Since then, you taught me music
女の肌もなめさせてくれた
And let me taste the skin of a woman
飲んだことねえ酒に口付けて
I sipped on drinks I'd never had before
音の煙草 薬に火を点けた
I lit up the tobacco and drugs of sound
やっちゃいけないが溢れてる
Overflowing with things we shouldn't do
しちゃいけないに守られてる
Protected by the forbidden acts
迎えに来る闇に紛れて
Mixing into the approaching darkness
お前はいつも気まぐれで
You're always so capricious
よふかしのうた
Call of the Night
照らしてって moonlight
Illuminate me, moonlight
目を奪って ブルーライト
Captivate my eyes, blue light
ネオンサインが呼ぶ
The neon signs are calling
表裏
Inside out
よふかしのうた
Call of the Night
連れ去って midnight
Take me away, midnight
血走った red eyes
With bloodshot red eyes
大人達の子守唄
Lullaby for the adults
なんせ俺達の夜は忙しい
Because our night is busy
Keep on dancin' さあ鬼の居ぬ間に
Keep on dancin' while the demon's away
俺達の夜は忙しい oh yeah
Our night is busy oh yeah
なんせ俺達の夜は忙しい
Because our night is busy
Keep on dancin' さあ鬼の居ぬ間に
Keep on dancin' while the demon's away
俺達の夜は忙しい oh yeah
Our night is busy oh yeah
晴れて大人の仲間入り
Finally joined the ranks of adults
若輩者が青で朝帰れ
Young and green, going home in the blue of morning
腫れ物触るような周りの目に中指立てども空回り
Flipping the bird at the eyes that avoid me like a sore spot, but it's in vain
暗い部屋照らしてってMoonlight
Light up the dark room, Moonlight
白くて固いダイヤル蹴った
Kicked the white and hard dial
認めたくないお前のせいさ
I don't want to admit it's your fault
起こさないでTeacher I'm a daydream believer
Don't wake me Teacher, I'm a daydream believer
俺の若さを日々吸い上げる
Sucking up my youth day by day
まるであの時のインキュバス
Just like the incubus from back then
近い内にケリつける
I'll settle this before long
お前に手をひかれて
With you leading me by the hand
眠たい土曜の溜まり場
To the sleepy Saturday hangout
同じ周波数のムジナ
Beasts on the same frequency
漏れなく社会的不適合者
All social misfits without exception
だけどお前は決して誰も責めない
But you never blame anyone
お前は決して何も聞かない
You never ask anything
お節介な日の光と違い 俺を正さない
Unlike the meddling sunlight, you don't correct me
未だお前を乗りこなせない
I still can't ride you well
未だお前を使い果たせない
I still can't use you up
ずっと今日が終わらない 明日は始められない
Today won't end, tomorrow can't start
よふかしのうた
Song of the Night
照らしてってmoonlight
Light it up moonlight
目を奪ってブルーライト
Dazzle my eyes blue light
ネオンサインが呼ぶ表と裏
Neon signs calling, front and back
よふかしのうた
Song of the Night
連れ去ってmidnight
Take me away midnight
血走ったredeyes
Bloodshot redeyes
大人達の子守唄
Lullaby for the adults
なんせ俺達の夜は忙しい
Because our night is busy
Keep on dancin' さあ鬼の居ぬ間に
Keep on dancin' while the demon's away
俺達の夜は忙しい oh yeah
Our night is busy oh yeah
なんせ俺達の夜は忙しい
Because our night is busy
Keep on dancin' さあ鬼の居ぬ間に
Keep on dancin' while the demon's away
俺達の夜は忙しい oh yeah
Our night is busy oh yeah
*Clears throat*
皆さん、Welcome one and all to my very special Halloween night concert, J-RAP in JIGOKU!
Everyone, welcome one and all to my very special Halloween night concert, J-RAP in JIGOKU!
I hope you guys are already having a great time!
The first song that I kicked off this concert with is "Yofukashi no Uta"...
...or in English, "A Staying Up Late Lullaby" or something like that.
It's my favorite Creepy Nuts song ever and I actually got to perform it with Creepy Nuts a while back...
...but that was a paid thing, a paid programming.
So this time, I got to perform it for you guys on this amazing stage!
Isn't it so awesome?
I feel like it really, like, it encapsulates the idea of J-RAP, which is my roots, by the way.
The theme of this concert is "Roots".
Like where do you come from, and you should never forget your roots. Well, my roots are in J-RAP.
Japanese rap, they always have been for many years ever since I came here to Japan...
...to be involved in the scene. Isn't it an amazing stage?
Look at it, we got graffiti everywhere! Oh my gosh, it's like...
...I mean it's graffiti, but it's very like Wafu.
...I mean it's graffiti, but it's very like Japanese-style.
なんか、日本のテイストも入ってるから本当に最高。
It's got some Japanese taste in it too, so it's really the best.
めっちゃめちゃいい感じ。かっこいいっすね、このステージ。
It feels great. This stage is so cool.
この素敵な舞台の上に色んな...
On this wonderful stage, various...
...J-RAP曲やってみたいと思います。
...J-RAP songs I'd like to perform.
And there's so many different kinds of J-RAP and different communities within the genre of J-RAP.
And so I tried to pick a lot of songs for the setlist that I guess are like very different from each other...
...but still Japanese rap. And, um...
...I think that you guys might also realize there's a bit of a story going on in between some of the songs...
...so I hope you guys will pay attention to that because that's also about my roots.
Moving on to the hashtag, the hashtag is #JRAPinJIGOKU.
Like I said, #JRAPinJIGOKU. I hope you guys will take lots of screenshots.
スクリーンショットいっぱい撮ってほしい！お願いします！
I want you to take lots of screenshots! Please!
はい！There's going to be a lot of really cool effects on the stage...
Yes! There's going to be a lot of really cool effects on the stage...
...like there's an audio spectrum on the ground that like...
...it like reacts to my vocals when I'm singing and stuff like that.
It's just... it's really cool. This is a dream live for me, so I hope you guys will enjoy!
We also have a lot of really amazing guests, some that are going to blow your mind.
すごい、とても素敵なゲストも来るから皆さん...
Some really great guests are coming, so everyone...
...見てください！これからもっと...
...please watch! From now on, more...
...なんか、え、え、どうしよう。
...like, uh, what should I do?
あ、派手にぶちかまそうぜ！
Ah, let's go all out!
そうですね、カリオペっぽいセリフ。
Right, a Calliope-like line.
Yeah, that's kind of my catchphrase these days.
Without further ado, let's move on to the next song!
Everyone, please enjoy and keep the party going! Let's go!
まつり
Lyrics, Music: Fujii Kaze
Matsuri
愛しか感じたくもない
I don't even want to feel anything but love
もうなんの揚げ足でもない
I'm no longer picking anyone's faults
まつりへ出かけてきなさい
Come out and join the festival
今まで全て受け止めるから
Because I'll accept everything up until now
だいたいなんか欲しいわけや
Basically, you want something, don't you?
誰に勝ちたいわけや
Who do you want to beat?
なかなか気付けんや
It's hard to notice, isn't it?
何もかも既に持ってるのにね
Even though you already have everything
花まつり
Flower festival
夏まつり
Summer festival
なんでも好きに選びな
Choose whatever you like
あなたの心の中　咲かせなさい
Let it bloom inside your heart
秋まつり
Autumn festival
冬休み
Winter break
その閉じた心　今こそ開けな
Now is the time to open that closed heart
らっせー
Rasse!
まつり　まつり
Festival, festival
毎日愛しき何かのまつり
Every day is a festival of something dear
まつり　まつり
Festival, festival
あれもこれもが有り難い
Everything and anything is a blessing
比べるものは何もない
There's nothing to compare it to
勝ち負けとかは一切ない
There's no winning or losing at all
ない
None
なんなんしたこっちゃない
I don't care what happens
好きにしてください
Please do as you like
なんなんしたこっちゃない
I don't care what happens
好きにしてください
Please do as you like
雨が激しく叩いてせいで
Because the rain was hitting hard
君が跳ねに跳ねてせいで
Because you were jumping and jumping
夏の暑さから炉焦がして
Burning the furnace from the summer heat
冬の厳しさ骨身にしみた
The winter's severity cut to the bone
まっさらに生きられたら
If I could live a brand new life
まっすぐにそこへ行けたかな
Could I have gone there directly?
しゃー　今なら遅くはないから
Shaa, it's not too late now
しゃー　しゃー　しゃー　しゃー
Shaa, shaa, shaa, shaa
花まつり
Flower festival
夏まつり
Summer festival
あんまり熱もなしに行くもの
Going without much enthusiasm
すべて解けてうちら出来上がり
Everything dissolves, and we're complete
秋まつり
Autumn festival
冬休み
Winter break
みんな抱きしめたら踊りなさい
Embrace everyone and dance
らっせー
Rasse!
まつり　まつり
Festival, festival
毎日愛しき何かのまつり
Every day is a festival of something dear
まつり　まつり
Festival, festival
あれもこれもが有り難い
Everything and anything is a blessing
苦しむことは何もない
There is nothing to suffer about
肩を落とすことは一切ない
There's no need to hang your head at all
まつり　まつり
Festival, festival
毎日愛しき何かのまつり
Every day is a festival of something dear
まつり　まつり
Festival, festival
あれもこれもが有り難い
Everything and anything is a blessing
苦しむことは何もない
There is nothing to suffer about
肩を落とすことは一切ない
There's no need to hang your head at all
なんなんしたこっちゃない
I don't care what happens
好きにしてください
Please do as you like
なんなんしたこっちゃない
I don't care what happens
何せおめでたい
Anyway, it's something to celebrate
Hey DJ! カマセ!
Hey DJ! Let's go!
Yeah yeah yeah!
気分上々↑↑の
Feeling high spirits
針を落とせ　音鳴らせ　party night
Drop the needle, sound the noise, party night
飲も　ライ　ライ　ライ
Let's drink, lie lie lie
みんなで踊れ!
Everyone, dance!
Hip hop pop　かけてよミラクルナンバー
Hip hop pop, play that miracle number
気分上々↑↑
Lyrics: hiroko, mitsuyuki miyake
Music: mitsuyuki miyake, Genki Hibino
Kibun Joujou↑↑
Lyrics: hiroko, mitsuyuki miyake
Music: mitsuyuki miyake, Genki Hibino
混な時代に価値あるmusic
Valuable music in these chaotic times
探して回す地球儀
Searching for it as I spin the globe
娯楽不安定生活だらけ　乱反射
A life full of unstable entertainment, diffuse reflection
良いことばかりじゃないから頑張れる
I can work hard because it's not always good things
サイクルにキック　再起動のボタンクリック
Kick the cycle, click the restart button
DJかけて今トリック
DJ, play it now, trick
弾けてるビートに乗って
Ride the bursting beat
感じ中体揺らそうよ
Feel it as you sway your body
Yeah...
Hey DJ! カマセ!
Hey DJ! Let's go!
Yeah yeah yeah!
気分上々↑↑の
Feeling high spirits
針を落とせ　音鳴らせ　party night
Drop the needle, sound the noise, party night
飲も　ライ　ライ　ライ
Let's drink, lie lie lie
みんなで踊れ！
Everyone, dance!
ヒップホップ
Hip-hop
かけてよミラクルナンバー
Play that miracle number
Ah Hip Hop I am Hip Hop
Techno House Rocket Pop
オリジナル探す Keep Voice
Searching for the original, keep voice
それぞれの色重ね合わせるインボ
Overlapping our respective colors, info
君に伝えたい事目一杯 閉めあげくの果て
So much I want to tell you, in the end...
意固地固め
Hardening my stubbornness
今を楽しみたいんだね Ready
You want to enjoy the now, right? Ready
Hip Hop Hip Pop Let's Go
♯フロアの上
#On the floor
頭の中
Inside my head
揺さ
Shaking
揺さぶる
Shaking it up
Hey DJ
シャシャれ Yeah Yeah Yeah
Show off, Yeah Yeah Yeah
気分上々の
Feeling great
波に乗って
Ride the wave
弾け飛べ ファンキーナイト
Burst out, funky night
飲もう ライ ライ ライ
Let's drink, lai lai lai
みんなで踊れ！
Everyone, dance!
ヒップホップ
Hip-hop
朝までミラクルナンバー
Miracle number until morning
ミラーボール瞬く間に
In the blink of an eye, the mirror ball...
溶け合うよハーモニー
...harmonizes and melts together.
身に纏って踊り明かす
Wrap yourself in it and dance through the night.
がむしゃらなままで
Just keep being reckless.
Hey DJ
カマせ Yeah Yeah Yeah
Let's do this, Yeah Yeah Yeah
気分上々の
Feeling great
針落とせ
Drop the needle
音鳴らせ パーリナイト
Make some noise, party night
飲もう ライ ライ ライ
Let's drink, lai lai lai
みんなで踊れ！
Everyone, dance!
ヒップホップ
Hip-hop
かけてよミラクルナンバー
Play that miracle number
Hey DJ
シャシャれ Yeah Yeah Yeah
Show off, Yeah Yeah Yeah
気分上々の
Feeling great
波に乗って
Ride the wave
弾け飛べ ファンキーナイト
Burst out, funky night
飲もう ライ ライ ライ
Let's drink, lai lai lai
みんなで踊れ！
Everyone, dance!
ヒップホップ
Hip-hop
朝までミラクルナンバー
Miracle number until morning
Hey DJ
カマせ Yeah Yeah Yeah
Let's do this, Yeah Yeah Yeah
飲もう ライ ライ ライ
Let's drink, lai lai lai
カマせ Yeah Yeah Yeah
Let's do this, Yeah Yeah Yeah
飲もう ライ ライ ライ
Let's drink, lai lai lai
カマせ Yeah Yeah Yeah
Let's do this, Yeah Yeah Yeah
飲もう ライ ライ ライ
Let's drink, lai lai lai
カマせ Yeah Yeah Yeah
Let's do this, Yeah Yeah Yeah
飲もう ライ ライ ライ
Let's drink, lai lai lai
Hey DJ
カマせ Yeah Yeah Yeah
Let's do this, Yeah Yeah Yeah
BAU BAU! BAU BAU!
Everyone, what did you think of our performance?
YAY! BAU BAU!
Okay, my turn. BAU BAU!
YAY! That was my biggest BAU BAU.
My biggest BAU BAU yet! Oh my god.
Thank you so much. It's hard to hold back the BAU BAU.
Since both of you are here, it's like I'm being overwhelmed.
But I'm so happy to have both of you here. Thank you so much! I'm so happy! YAY!
Wow. And for those that don't know, jiko-shoukai onegaishimasu!
Wow. And for those that don't know, self-introductions, please!
I love Chihuahua! I'm Fuwawa!
I love Chihuahua! I'm Mococo!
Together we are FuwaMoco! BAU BAU!
And I'm Mori! YAY! Calli-chou! YAY!
Yeah, that was so fun. Thank you so much you guys.
That was so much fun! YAY!
I love dancing with you guys and learning the dance together...
...and singing...
...this move...
...and then the robot!
Yeah! It was so cool!
So fun. I'll never forget it. I have so many unforgettable experiences with you guys.
Like when we went to the onsen!
ONSEN! ONSEN! That was so much fun!
We-we had a bit of mishaps. Yeah, there was a mishap.
There was a misunderstanding. Mishap! Misunderstanding!
Yeah, everybody went into the kake-mizu...
...because I thought it was the koto-yu!
It's me! Calli! There was no sign that said don't come in here.
No, no sign! It didn't say no nothing!
Kake-mizu, you can pour the water...
...so you just thought it was like a small bath! Yeah!
But when it's for baths, but...
もう入らないね。
We won't go in anymore.
入っちゃったね。
We did go in though.
災難だった。
It was a disaster.
ごめんなさい。
Sorry.
BAU BAU! We didn't know! It was a misunderstanding.
But it's okay! It's a good memory!
I feel like we need to hit the onsen after this.
Let's go right after!
Right after, right after the show.
But for now, I'm doing this big show centered around J-RAP.
Please!
I want to know, what are you guys' roots?
Roots?
Of course! BAU BAU!
We really, really like idols and anime songs.
Yeah.
So I think that's our roots.
You guys' roots. Such nice roots.
Yeah, but you know, J-Rock also fits in that rap, too!
Yes, yes!
So we're super happy to see KIBOJOJO today!
Yay!
Yeah! There could have been no one better to perform this song with.
So, thank you so much, FuwaMoco!
Thank you so much!
Thank you so much! It was so fun, you guys!
Yeah!
Let's hang out again soon and dance together, okay?
Definitely, definitely! Okay!
Have the best rest of today!
Thank you! Ganba-ba-i!
Ganba-ba-i!
Before we say goodbye, can I get a hug?
Yeah! Come on!
BAU BAU!
BAU BAU! Thank you! Bye-bye!
Bye-bye! See you! Bye-bye!
The loudest bau baus ever.
Well, I'm feeling very energized.
Those two are the best. And honestly, I feel ready to talk about the next part of my roots.
I hope you guys will enjoy the story as it's unfolding.
Kind of like my life, I don't know.
Um, are you guys ready for the next part?
Let's keep enjoying the show together.
And, um, and yeah. Please enjoy.
どうぞ。
Please enjoy.
The days I can't get back...
Days we spent singing and laughing and not caring.
There was peace in that hectic time.
"Maybe someday I can go on a musical adventure with my friends, too!"
"Just like those performers I admire so much."
But...
I was already on one.
I just didn't see it.
Night after night, in a strange country full of words I didn't understand,
unfamiliar things were everywhere and yet...
They became irreplaceable.
So then... how were any of us to know?
It wasn't meant to last.
Hey there.
Don't suppose that's where all the trouble began...?
皆さん、今日のライブに来てくれてありがとうございます。Thank you so much!
Everyone, thank you for coming to today's live performance. Thank you so much!
This song is my roots.
この曲のおかげで、こんな素敵なステージの上に立っています。
Thanks to this song, I am standing on such a wonderful stage.
なんか、すごい感謝してます。
I'm just so grateful.
Let's do this! Come on, Reine! Here we go!
演出しようか びっと出番
Let's put on a show, it's Bit's turn
混ぜる このアレびと スタートライン
Mix it up, this is Rapbit's start line
超絶にオーガナイズ
Transcendentally organized,
いわゆるブログ 始動 スタートライン
the so-called blog starts, start line
ジャンキー 自由に 越して 遊ぼうぜ
Junkie, go over it freely and let's play
だって 俺ら 地区 代表
After all, we're the regional representatives
ドンドン 乗っけんだよ
Keep piling it on
ドンドン 録っても 楽しんだもん
Keep recording it, we're having fun
ガチで勝負だぜ べリスキャンザバース
This is a real showdown, scanning the verse
おのれをのせ 手に掴んだら
Put yourself on it, and once you grasp it...
真剣勝負 振る舞いたい ショー マスト ゴー オン
I want to act in a serious match, the show must go on
真剣勝負 ぶっ放したい ショー マスト ゴー オン
I want to fire off in a serious match, the show must go on
Alright, you better open the door!
Alright, get ready onto the floor!
全部 背負ったまま 降りろ
Get down while carrying it all
今は 撃ち抜くための 弾丸を リロード
Now, reload the bullets to shoot through
俺ら オーディエンス 沸かすだけ
We just hype the audience
音に乗ってく ローテク 皿回せ
Getting on the sound, low-tech, spin the record
オーディエンス 沸かせた程度の 能力
The ability to move an audience
ばらまく この宇宙に
Scattering it into this universe
少しでも明日へだろう 歩こう
Let's walk toward tomorrow, even just a bit
アンコールの 向こうへと
Beyond the encore
誘う 君と 次の 街へ
I'll lead you to the next town
回り出した ミラーボール
The mirror ball has started spinning
一瞬一瞬を 瞳に
Keeping every single moment in our eyes
バインドシングアソング 地球儀を回せ
Bind, sing a song, spin the globe
Get it back!
呼吸は ずっと 続きだ 贅沢
Breathing keeps going on, a luxury
悪いわ 四六時中 贅沢
I feel bad, luxury all day long
鳴るようなハニーと一大事 計画へ
To the big plan with a honey-like sound
末広がり
Prosperity
二人の打撃が振る
Two blows fall
不特定多数を襲う奴
Those who attack an unspecified many
奴のステータスなど即制圧
Suppressing their status in an instant
凄く贅沢に楽しもうぜ
Let's enjoy it in a very luxurious way
Hey Yo, Watch the stage
Come on! Rap Beat-o!
Oh, Watch Watch What? The Magic of Cinderella
Underground THE SAME Everybody, What you want?
Feel like 処置遅延よりが欲しい
Feel like I want it more than a delayed treatment
指ばっか詰めた武器屋に星
Starring the weapon shop filled with only fingers
Catch me the energy beatの元
Catch me the energy beat's source
大関・観覧・一分間のSHOW
Ozeki, viewing, a one-minute SHOW
夢で再会 一度きりの
Meeting again in a dream, for the only time
君との指切りの約束
A pinky promise with you
俺らオーディエンス沸かすだけ
We're just getting the audience fired up
音に乗って ローテク皿回せ
Ride the sound, spin the low-tech records
オーディエンス沸かせた程度の
With the level of skill that just gets an audience fired up
能力ばら撒く この宇宙に
I'll scatter my power throughout this universe
少しでも明日へだろう
Toward tomorrow, even if just a little
歩こう アンコールの向こうへと
Let's walk toward the other side of the encore
君と次の街へ
To the next city with you
誘う 君と次の街へ
Inviting you to the next city
目指した未来を 記憶集め 再び
Aiming for the future, gathering memories once again
一つになって Sing a Song 地球儀を回せ
Becoming one, Sing a Song, spin the globe
Yeah! Bounce let me Bounce いたいたけになっても
Yeah! Bounce let me Bounce, even if I become pathetic
独自のセンスで皆 来な
Come along everyone, with your unique sense
迷いなんて無い 無理な話
There's no hesitation, that's out of the question
真夜中のような時代に
In an era like the middle of the night
悪評も聞こえる 枠の外
I can hear the bad reputation from outside the frame
こちとらガチだぜ Rapをオーダー
I'm dead serious here, ordering up some Rap
100万回 拡大のSHOW
A SHOW expanded a million times
俺らRap以外にゃ 全く無い
We have absolutely nothing but Rap
ゆらり揺れる ローソクの火
The flickering flame of a candle
放っておきゃ消える 尊い一瞬
A precious moment that disappears if left alone
すら気付ける 崇高な楽しみ
A noble pleasure that one can even notice
合言葉は バカバカ
The password is "Idiot, Idiot"
やっぱ クラブなら TRAP TRAP
After all, if it's a club, it's TRAP TRAP
武士も最高 TRAP TRAP TRAP
The samurai is also great, TRAP TRAP TRAP
オーディエンスは TRAP TRAP
The audience is TRAP TRAP
何の問題も無い どフラットSHOW
A perfectly flat SHOW with no issues at all
3, 2, 1
俺らオーディエンス沸かすだけ
We're just getting the audience fired up
音に乗って ローテク皿回せ
Ride the sound, spin the low-tech records
オーディエンス沸かせた程度の
With the level of skill that just gets an audience fired up
能力ばら撒く この宇宙に
I'll scatter my power throughout this universe
少しでも明日へだろう
Toward tomorrow, even if just a little
歩こう アンコールの向こうへと
Let's walk toward the other side of the encore
君と次の街へ
To the next city with you
誘う 君と次の街へ
Inviting you to the next city
俺らオーディエンス沸かすだけ
We're just getting the audience fired up
オーディエンス沸かすだけ
みんな 本当にありがとう
Everyone, thank you so much
We are Chu-Oku
マイク片手に分からす 中毒
With a mic in one hand, making them understand the addiction
We are Chu-Oku
Check it out, We are 言の葉党
Check it out, we are the Kotonoha Party
さあ堂々と通れ 通と言の葉を侍らす
Now pass through proudly, attending to the truth and words
其処 退け 男共 さあ長名乗らせ
Move aside, men, let the leader state her name
此方と御手 乙女の意のままに 遊ぶ
With this hand, playing as the maiden wishes
Okay さあ跪け 安んじご覧遊ばせ
Okay, now kneel, and look on at your leisure
此れが私のマニフェスト ボディ
This is my manifesto, body
姿替え術 敵にも成れねえ
Shape-shifting technique, you can't even become my enemy
噛み付くの御免 有れ無しのBEEF
Forgive me for biting, beef that may or may not exist
気安く呼んでんじゃねえよ Bad Queens
Don't call me so casually, Bad Queens
其の穴に嵌まり 抗う術無し ジリジリ
Falling into that hole, with no way to resist, bit by bit
オフィシャルからアイまで固め ほら
Securing everything from official to eye, look
TOPしか似合わん この宿命
This fate that only suits the top
伊達の眼に覚えとけよ名前
Remember my name in your discerning eyes
風の如し 暗路の先 照らす定め
Like the wind, fated to light the dark road ahead
Shut up, Shut up そんなんじゃダメ
Shut up, shut up, that's no good
甘い ぬるい 借り物言葉じゃ飛べないでしょ
Sweet, lukewarm, you can't fly with borrowed words, can you?
蛇の這う道にも レスト・イン・ピース
Even on the path where snakes crawl, rest in peace
待たれん 賞賛 葉っぱも結構
Praise I won't wait for, fluff is also fine
お手が出る 余興でしょ?
A helping hand appears, it's just a sideshow, right?
私がName これがMaster piece
I am the Name, this is the Masterpiece
強様言霊に 跪くのよ ボーイズ
Kneel before the powerful spirit of language, boys
西から東へ さあ道を進め
From west to east, now proceed along the path
我々がルール 革命のSHOW
We are the rules, the SHOW of revolution
最後に笑うのは 乙女にせよ
Let the one who laughs last be a maiden
東から西へ さあ頂上目指せ
From east to west, now aim for the top
我々がルール 革命のSHOW
We are the rules, the SHOW of revolution
もっと試したい己
I want to test myself even more
We are Chu-Oku
マイク片手に分からす 中毒
With a mic in one hand, making them understand the addiction
We are Chu-Oku
Check it out, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1, ZECK!
今 示しますのよ 番付
Now I will show you the rankings
限界 飛び交う ボイス
Voices flying across the limit
上げて来いよ 糞兵隊
Bring it up, you crappy soldiers
天下の現状 目眩起きるわ Wake up
The current state of the world makes me dizzy, wake up
Hands Up, Hands Up 今から底見舞いする 電車
Hands Up, Hands Up, a train heading for a sudden visit to the bottom
ぴょんぴょん跳ねてバウンド天板
Hopping and bouncing on the top plate
取りまとめるビッジョーからのディビジョン
Taking control of the divisions from the top
目立つ上げ 本物だれ？
Standing out, who's the real deal?
フラッシュクラクラさせてく 言の葉アンサン
Make them dizzy with the flash, the Kotonoha ensemble
斬り開け 未踏の地
Cut through to uncharted lands
乗りこなす グルーヴ
Riding the groove
お手本見せようか 身を任せ
Shall I show you how it's done? Surrender yourself
Yeah My Main Flow 磨く苦労 白々
Yeah, my main flow, the effort to polish it, so obvious
と真似事爆破
And blowing up the imitations
躾の行き届いたこのメロ
This well-disciplined melody
隙のなさが売りで Savage go
My selling point is having no openings, Savage go
右へ左へ
To the right, to the left
雑踏と進め
Advance through the crowd
我らエンガール革命のショー
We are the En-Girl revolution show
最後に笑うのは乙女に女神
The ones laughing at the end are the maidens and goddesses
西へ東へ
To the west, to the east
さあ頂上目指せ
Come, aim for the top
我らエンガール革命のショー
We are the En-Girl revolution show
もっと試したいおのれを
I want to test myself even more
落とせ 落とせ
Bring them down, bring them down
澄み渡す貴様の情報さ
Your information becomes clear
落とせ 落とせ
Bring them down, bring them down
三人寄ればたちまちかしまし
When three of us gather, it's instantly boisterous
攻防戦 落とせ 落とせ
An offensive and defensive battle, bring them down
言葉の弾丸さあ撃ち刻め
Bullets of words, come, shoot and carve them in
Oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah
任せな
Leave it to me
革命の時間だ
It's time for revolution
Oh yeah We are 中王
Oh yeah, we are Chu-oh
マイク片手に分からす忠告
Giving you a warning with a mic in hand
Oh yeah We are 中王
Oh yeah, we are Chu-oh
Check it out we are 言の葉党
Check it out, we are the Party of Words
Come on we are 中王
Come on, we are Chu-oh
ペン走らす得に中毒
Addicted to letting the pen run
Oh yeah we are 中王
Oh yeah, we are Chu-oh
Check it out we are 言の葉党
Check it out, we are the Party of Words
急所突き一発
A single strike to the vital point
空前絶後 無双だし
Unprecedented and unparalleled
ほら見ろ他と違うぜ
Look, we're different from the rest
我らの品格は五感
Our dignity lies in the five senses
Check it out we are 言の葉党
Check it out, we are the Party of Words
Hey! Come shut up!
It's me, Mori and Bae! From PROMISE! Let's go!
共闘
Joint Struggle (Kyoutou)
溜息混じりに触れる Oh my god
Touching with a mix of sighs, Oh my god
燃やして照らしてラッタッタ
Burn it up, light it up, rattatta
余裕かまして温存した全反動を吐き出すのさ
Spitting out all the recoil I saved up while keeping my cool
勇ましく行こうか
Shall we go bravely?
容易さ 簡単にゃ生まれねえし
It's easy, though it's not born easily
この状況打開する策があるのかい
Is there a plan to break this situation?
Oh, that's right! 任せときな
Oh, that's right! Leave it to us
時は来んぜ ほら行け
The time has come, look, go
デカい口叩く奴を ヒットの常連じゃいられない
Those who talk big can't stay on the charts forever
ジェラシーばら撒くヒーロー 呆れて暴れてナンボ
A hero scattering jealousy, it's all about going wild in amazement
逆転の発想
Thinking in reverse
共闘さ
It's a joint struggle
Let's get back 暴れ出すサイン
Let's get back, the sign of going wild
瞳を返すならお早めに
If you're going to turn your eyes away, do it soon
目まぐるしい様な展開が 今始まるんだ
A dizzying development is beginning right now
Let's get high 止まる気はない
Let's get high, I have no intention of stopping
手のひら返しならお早めに
If you're going to flip-flop, do it soon
な？ 僕らの想像を超えて ぶっ飛んでった SO FAR
See? Exceeding our imagination, we've flown SO FAR
研ぎ澄ませ 魂は一発限りだ
Sharpen yourself, your soul only has one shot
MOVING を決めたらモダナイズ振るい出
Once you've decided on the MOVING, shake out the modernization
狂おしく ルージン 邪念も無視して
Going crazy, loozin, ignoring all idle thoughts
うっせえ うっせえわ
Shut up, shut the hell up
サバイブしに行くしかないのさ 挑戦状
We have no choice but to go survive, here's a challenge
火花散らすため 勝ち上がる
To make sparks fly, we'll rise to victory
いざ 想像を絶する 環境も佳境も
Now, beyond imagination, both the environment and the climax
上等だ
Bring it on
Let's get back 見逃すなサイン
Let's get back, don't miss the sign
どんでん返しならお墨付き
A complete turnaround is guaranteed
夢の様な光景は目を見開け見るんだ
Open your eyes wide and see this dream-like sight
Let's get high 許されぬミス
Let's get high, an unforgivable mistake
裏をかく土壇場 おもてなし
Hospitality at the last moment by outsmarting them
棒に振りはしない フルスイングで ぶっ飛んでいけ SO FAR
I won't let it go to waste, go fly SO FAR with a full swing
再三再四 次は君の番
Time and time again, next is your turn
我慢も白旗も しまったまま
Patience and white flags, keep them tucked away
Do or Die もうやっちゃったわ
Do or Die, I've already done it
Let's go Let's go Let's go
共闘さ
It's a joint struggle
Let's get back 暴れ出すサイン
Let's get back, the sign of going wild
瞬き厳禁で
No blinking allowed
さあ Let's get back 暴れ出すサイン
Now, let's get back, the sign of going wild
瞳を返すならお早めに
If you're going to turn your eyes away, do it soon
目まぐるしい様な展開が 今始まるんだ
A dizzying development is beginning right now
Let's get high 止まる気はない
Let's get high, I have no intention of stopping
手のひら返しならお早めに
If you're going to flip-flop, do it soon
な？ 僕らの想像を超えて ぶっ飛んでった SO FAR
See? Exceeding our imagination, we've flown SO FAR
ぶっ飛んでいけ SO FAR
Fly away, SO FAR
Wow! Hah!
Hey, I see you ninja running around my stage, oi! All these young people...
You guys have so much freaking energy!
Jesus!
Hello!
Everybody, Baelz Take!
What's up! I am Chaos, the end of ends, I still rat's trap in the cage of ice,
your best friend Baelz Take from Hololive English Council, Baeos Take!
That was dramatic. In a good way, though. In a good way.
Thank you, thank you.
Callie! Happy Halloween!
Happy Halloween!
Ooooh. Welcome to J-Rap in Jigoku. Thank you so much for the two songs.
Yeah! Thank you so much for inviting me. I had so much fun.
What was that choreo, man? I don't even know what was that choreo.
The this? Oh, the this? And then the this? Oh, the this?
Yeah! It was so much fun.
That's way more than I'm used to. But... but it was fun. I had to pull out all the stops.
I'm so proud of you. You did so good. Thank you. You did so good. She did so good, everyone.
I gotta get my stamina back. I'm so shaky.
Listen, Bae, the theme of this whole deal is roots. So like, what are your roots like?
What what are you like? I don't know, it feels already obvious. Go on then, starting with.
What are my roots? Well, I guess I started... I loved music from a young age. I also loved dance from a young age. Yeah.
Whoa, look at those fancy moves! Fancy move! What the heck?
So I guess I started as a dancer. That is my roots. I love performing and I hope to continue to be able to perform for everyone who wants to watch.
Yeah! Heck yeah! You know, Bae actually had a show recently.
Yeah! I hope everyone enjoyed!
Check it out on her channel. It's really, really awesome.
Oh my goodness. I nearly... that was the end. I nearly... everything was ended after that, my goodness.
I feel you, seriously.
Well, thank you so much for coming today, Bae. Let's hang out again.
Thank you so much! Yeah, I want to hang out again.
Let's do it. Whether it be, you know, dancing. Yeah, or otherwise.
Oh my god, she's good at it! Stop, stop! That's awesome.
Alright, see you later, Bae! Thanks again!
See you later! Thanks for having me! Have fun for the rest of the show! Bye-bye!
Ha... I guess we're going onto the next part of the show.
Next up, you're going to see a video that is part 3, the finale of, I guess, some kind of like, I don't know, movie about my roots.
And after that, I've got something very special to share with you guys.
A special reveal of a brand new me! So I hope you guys will enjoy it.
While you guys watch that, I'm gonna go catch my breath. Please keep enjoying J-Rap in Jigoku. Peace.
They shut it all down.
The miasma that permeated this town did its job,
and the people I ran through those nights with...
Just kind of... disappeared.
Back to real life.
They left the dream.
“How am I supposed to go back?”
“This music is the only reason I’m here.”
“There’s nothing left back there for me.”
“In a land where I lost my identity.”
“If there’s no more music here, then I have no choice but to go home.”
It was music that brought me to this country.
It was music that kept me here.
But...
It was a hand that reached out at that moment
that I thought I’d never hear an inspiring melody again.
Maybe it was never the “end of a life.”
It was the continuation of a story...
My story.
That stage went dark, but ya know...
You never really forget where you came from.
GILA GILA
Hah, いるの legacy
Hah, I'm a legacy
違う energy
Different energy
病める民がもっとも好む言葉が therapy
The word the sick people like the most is therapy
Bitch, don't pick me
君なら enemy
If it's you, you're an enemy
Tightに放す stunner 登ってくこの pyramid
I release a tight stunner, climbing this pyramid
女神降臨 増える damage
The goddess descends, damage increases
Burst 蹴れば spinning bird kicks まるで Chun-Li
When I burst and kick, it's like spinning bird kicks, just like Chun-Li
Holy Trinity
Money, Power, Fame 全て Get, everything なんて思い描く grind
Money, Power, Fame, get it all, get everything, that's the grind I envision
働く汗昼の bar, next place 死ぬまで bar
Sweat from working at a bar during the day, the next place is also a bar until I die
悩みも焦りも全部 光に変えてみせ
I'll turn all my worries and impatience into light
MS腕立てから何ヒット？
How many hits since MS push-ups?
鳴き続きはないヒット
No consecutive hits for crying
ヒットしてないヒットにも
Even the hits that didn't hit
言われるお前は誰？
ask you, who are you?
愛すならまず退ける あの日ワズが言ってた事
If you love, step aside first. What Waz said that day.
天国から見守る 死ぬ前のあいつも言っていた
Watching from heaven. That guy said it too, before he died.
逃げられない今更 水晶に仕掛ける罠
Can't escape now. A trap set in the crystal.
Give me Gucci, Pucci and Prada 急いで着て Abercrombie
Give me Gucci, Pucci and Prada. Quickly put on Abercrombie.
I don't got time to play with you 黄泉の鐘が掛かる
I don't got time to play with you. The bell of Hades tolls.
耳をかっぽじって聞きな 耳揃えてすぐに Pay off
Clean out your ears and listen. Put it all together and pay off immediately.
ギラギラ ギンギンギラ Ice on ice on killer
Glittering, shining. Ice on ice on killer.
ジャラジャラ Million dollar Ice on ice on killer
Jingling, million dollar. Ice on ice on killer.
ギラギラ ギンギンギラ Ice on ice on killer
Glittering, shining. Ice on ice on killer.
ヘイターズお疲れ様 Work hard 首元ならキラキラ
Haters, thanks for your hard work. Work hard, the neck is sparkling.
混ざり気ない純100％のVVSのチェーン 足元からほらほら
Pure 100% VVS chain. Look from the feet, see?
違いがわかるこの立ち方 靴ならDior たちも
The way I stand shows the difference. If it's shoes, Dior, even they...
ヒットヒットヒット ずっとリート きっと ヘイターズ ずっと シット
Hit hit hit. Always lead. Surely, haters always shit.
一歩一歩ずっと走り出す Shit Do it 一緒 俺鳴る Shikkyo
Step by step, always running out. Shit, do it together, my sound is death.
A-Zに呼ばれてどれだけが Set set set
Called by A-Z, how many are set set set?
Alexに下ろして作ってもらったこの Drip
Got this drip custom made by Alex.
いくら稼いでも足りねえ円 やりたいことに Bet bet bet
No matter how much I earn, it's not enough Yen. Bet bet bet on what I want to do.
投資して若稼ぐから倍にしなけども天の神にちょっと相談
Investing and earning while young, double it, but consult the God of Heaven for a bit.
相心の調子はどう？I ran to the wiseもアイスボックスでBust down
How's your state of mind? Even 'I ran to the wise' is bust down in the icebox.
犬もそこで声 有言実行スノーカップサバやりたいことが言ってたらたまたま叶っとり
Even the dog's voice there. Keeping my word, Snow Cup Saba. If you say what you want to do, it just happens to come true.
この3人なら立ちまちバズったり 欲しいものなら手に入れる片っ端
With these three, we'll go viral in no time. Get whatever you want, one after another.
馬鹿にしてた奴らは赤っ恥
Those who made fun of us are in deep shame.
Woah woah 出始めから右肩上がり 待て気付いてないように奴ばかり
Woah woah, soaring from the start. Wait, there are only those who haven't noticed.
音の上で俺生意気盛り
On the sound, I'm at the peak of my cockiness.
Woah woah 俺の乗る波のウェイ やれること制限はねえ
Woah woah, on the wave I ride. There's no limit to what I can do.
この口で稼ぐ円
The Yen I earn with this mouth.
なかなかこうも上手くいかないと思うけど Real life
I think it doesn't always go this well, but that's real life.
稼ぐ額増やすぜ去年の倍 Okay
I'll increase the amount I earn, double last year's. Okay.
ギラギラ ギンギンギラ Ice on ice on killer
Glittering, shining. Ice on ice on killer.
ジャラジャラ Million dollar Ice on ice on killer
Jingling, million dollar. Ice on ice on killer.
ギラギラ ギンギンギラ Ice on ice on killer
Glittering, shining. Ice on ice on killer.
ヘイターズお疲れ様 Work hard, play hard
Haters, thanks for your hard work. Work hard, play hard.
ゲトー高みから一抜け切った 川崎生まれのB-Boy da
I've broken out from the ghetto heights. I'm a B-Boy born in Kawasaki.
ただのBad boyからなるビリオネア 口座に積んでる今9桁
A billionaire made from a mere bad boy. Now 9 digits piled in the account.
キラキラってあいつはジェラス 嫌いな奴らが狙
Shinning, and he's jealous. The ones I hate are the target.
ダラダラしたら馬鹿 Magic cityでバラまくダラー
If you're lazy, you're a fool. Scattering dollars in Magic City.
可愛いあの子もこっち来た ソファーにゆっくり腰掛けて
That cute girl came here too. Sitting slowly on the sofa.
オールドヴィントンの骨董店 会計男気でジャンケン
Old Vinton's antique shop. Rock-paper-scissors to see who pays like a man.
今は好きなものチョイスしてるから未来のビジネス投資してる
Now I'm choosing what I like, so I'm investing in future business.
ジョービに全てを使いちまってる 寒すぎ今頃凍死してる
I've used it all up on equipment. It's too cold, I'm freezing to death about now.
ゾクゾク 規模は上がってくセイド 見つめるエイムは高彩度
Thrilling, the scale is rising. The aim I'm watching is high saturation.
ここまで来て爆死才能 これ闇の中でフルサイクル
Coming this far, a talent for exploding. This is a full cycle in the darkness.
後先より全額ベット 当てれば一夜にして天国
Betting everything regardless of the future. If I win, it's heaven overnight.
スリ買い取り凍える監獄 夢から醒め今から交渉
Pickpocketing and buying, a freezing prison. Waking from the dream, now for the negotiation.
数億円する商談 藤原ヒロシの履いてるJordan
A business deal worth hundreds of millions. Jordan shoes worn by Hiroshi Fujiwara.
お前じゃ割れない俺らの冗談 痛細かいかも狙く勝じゃん
You can't break our jokes. It might be painful and meticulous, but it's a win for the aim.
ゼロから手にした二つの勝算 あいつのヘイトもおカネと交換
Two chances of winning obtained from zero. Exchange his hate for money too.
極経が指してるてっぺんと王冠 お前との間に線引くボーダー
The pole points to the top and the crown. Drawing a border line between you and me.
Tsunami wave 夜街に降らす雨
Tsunami wave. Rain falling on the night city.
ひまるでピカチュウ ぴかぴか過ぎて痺れさせるチェーン
Just like Pikachu. A chain so bright it makes you numb.
ギラギラ ギンギンギラ Ice on ice on killer
Glittering, shining. Ice on ice on killer.
ジャラジャラ Million dollar Ice on ice on killer
Jingling, million dollar. Ice on ice on killer.
ギラギラ ギンギンギラ Ice on ice on killer
Glittering, shining. Ice on ice on killer.
ヘイターズお疲れ様 Work hard, play hard
Haters, thanks for your hard work. Work hard, play hard.
Ahem! 皆さん！
Ahem! Everyone!
What do you guys think?
We did it! The powers that be finally gave me...
...a brushed up version of of me, a brand new form.
What do you think? I wanted to reveal it in like a really exciting way,
so, I decided, uh, let's do it up here at the top of the castle!
こんな素敵なお城...で...
In such a wonderful castle...
めちゃくちゃ何かかっこいい だからめちゃめちゃ良い景色だから ここで歌ってみたいかなと思いました。
It's, like, super cool. And the view is so amazing, so I thought I'd like to try singing here.
I thought maybe I would sing here at the top of the castle...
...to reveal this brand new, it's not an outfit, it's it's basically a new body.
And this is what I'll be using from now on, this version of me.
So, I hope that you guys enjoy it. I'll probably go into more detail about it...
...and like show you in more detail during the members only stream.
That's right, we are doing one of those and everyone is welcome, if you're a member.
So, please be sure to join membership, okay?
And you might get a chance to see the old me again pretty soon here.
I get a feeling that, you know, we haven't fully closed out that chapter well, so...
we gotta do that, right?
Keep your eyes peeled. But for now, I want you guys to look really close at this...
...amazing, amazing setting that we have here.
うわあ、キラキラ！
Whoa, it's sparkling!
The walls are like glittering and stuff like that and the color is like...
I don't know, it's very shiny
and おしゃれ…　うーん！
and stylish... mmm!
So, I hope that you guys liked that
maybe a little overdone reveal.
But yeah! Witness!
Witness the power of the cooler,
Calliope Mori!
I'm still a little... I'm still a little lame though.
Sorry about that. I can't really fix that.
But for now, let's keep enjoying J-RAP together, okay?
Keep your eyes peeled.
And, 次に行きます！ Let's go!
And, let's go to the next one! Let's go!
DJ play that music louder, お願い
DJ play that music louder, please
Boom clap, boom-ba-boom clap. Boom clap, boom-ba-boom clap.
miss you
Lyrics, Music: m-flo, melody., 山本領平
Lyrics, Music: m-flo, melody., Ryohei Yamamoto
二人でいるのに
Even though we're together
近くにいても boy
Even if you're close, boy
少しだけ be-bear
Just a little, be-bear
(Kyu-kyu-kyu crush, love is mystery)
もしかして be-bear
Could it be, be-bear
(U say 's flow in this year)
気が変わる前に run
Run before my mind changes
そして今日もこのまま
And today as well, just like this
どこまでも少しだけ
Just a little bit more, everywhere
そうして朝まで ah ah ah in the atmosphere
And so until morning, ah ah ah in the atmosphere
Don't know why this love got to be 難しい
Don't know why this love has to be so difficult
I'm the 宇宙の super lover, ba-ba-ba なのに
Even though I'm the universe's super lover, ba-ba-ba
Don't know why this 手放したくないの be
Don't know why I don't want to let go
Gotta be so fly when U hear the melody, now listen
Gotta be so fly when you hear the melody, now listen
I don't know why, ki-ki-keep in touch with U
I don't know why, ki-ki-keep in touch with you
とても high に何もかも so upside down
Everything becomes so upside down, even when I'm so high
何もかもプレゼントされても baby don't U know
Even if I'm given everything as a present, baby don't you know
それだけじゃないよ
That's not all
I don't know why 好きなのに悩みよりも
I don't know why, even though I like you, more than worries
何て言いたいよ Is that bright girl?
What I want to say is, is that a bright girl?
賢いかどうかで代わるもの何でも出しても
Whether I'm smart or not, even if I put out anything that changes
幸せそうなの
You look happy
あげてどうさげてかざれるものは
Raising it, lowering it, the things that can be decorated
夢のようだけど Diamonds are forever
It's like a dream, but diamonds are forever
Melody, 宇宙船で bling
Melody, bling in the spaceship
Just anything 好きの光まで baby come close to me
Just anything, even the light of love, baby come close to me
Baby can't you see
わかってほしい this is my 気持ち
I want you to understand, this is my feeling
U gotta tell me 好きだなんてない
You gotta tell me, there's no such thing as 'I like you'
好きなもの倍して lalalala
Multiplying the things I like, lalalala
Who is it? Just me?
今日もないしょ
Secret again today
どうしても知り
Whatever happens, I know
教えて so I can do it right
Tell me, so I can do it right
Tonight U and I can just stop
Tonight you and I can just stop
二人でいるのに
Even though we're together
近くにいても boy
Even if you're close, boy
少しだけ be-bear
Just a little, be-bear
(Kyu-kyu-kyu crush, love is mystery)
もしかして be-bear
Could it be, be-bear
(U say 's flow in this year)
気が変わる前に run
Run before my mind changes
そして今日もこのまま
And today as well, just like this
どこまでも少しだけ
Just a little bit more, everywhere
そうして朝まで ah ah ah in the atmosphere
And so until morning, ah ah ah in the atmosphere
Boom clap, boom-ba-boom clap. Boom clap, boom-ba-boom clap.
A-yo, one, Tokyo minit でみせる love
A-yo, one, showing love in a Tokyo minute
I got a lot of it まだ dynamite 爆発 love
I got a lot of it, still dynamite exploding love
君は hot hot
You are hot hot
Hot hot
どうしたらいいでしょうか Cafe mocha
What should I do? Cafe mocha
Hot hot
誰もが振り向いて jealousy とけ散らす
Everyone turns around and scatters the jealousy
アツアツ she killin' me
Sizzling hot, she's killing me
Lalalalalalalalalalala
もっともっと like Stevie
More and more like Stevie
Sun steel delivery
好きなこと do it baby
Do what you like, do it baby
口紅無敵
Invincible lipstick
Can we まじめに二人で
Can we seriously, the two of us
Rock rock if U don't mind
Rock rock if you don't mind
噂を追えば this is all about
If you follow the rumors, this is all about
今の時変えないものだから
Because it's something you can't change in the present moment
Never on time 太陽ほほえみ
Never on time, the sun smiles
Hear your melody lalalalalala
How can I, can I, can I 耐えれば
How can I, can I, can I endure it
Just spend some time with me 考えな so please
Just spend some time with me, don't think about it, so please
もしも midnight に二人が
If the two of us are together at midnight
Gotta be lovin' 激しく hot ah ah ah
Gotta be lovin' intensely hot ah ah ah
二人でいるのに
Even though we're together
近くにいても boy
Even if you're close, boy
少しだけ be-bear
Just a little, be-bear
(Kyu-kyu-kyu crush, love is mystery)
もしかして be-bear
Could it be, be-bear
(U say 's flow in this year)
気が変わる前に run
Run before my mind changes
そして今日もこのまま
And today as well, just like this
どこまでも少しだけ
Just a little bit more, everywhere
そうして朝まで ah ah ah in the atmosphere
And so until morning, ah ah ah in the atmosphere
DJ play that music louder, お願い
DJ play that music louder, please
Ooh hai, how U like me now listen
Ooh high, how you like me now listen
Lala 聞こえてきたら
Lala, if you can hear it
No, 壊せの常習 survive it all
No, break the common practice, survive it all
A-yo the way I'm livin' is five stars
A-yo the way I'm living is five stars
Let's go large, 超未来 go
Let's go large, super future go
Hit the floor U my type
Hit the floor you're my type
What's your name, 止まらなく over
What's your name, stopping for no one, over
Throw your hands up in the air
Come on baby girl 流れ星みたいな feeling
Come on baby girl, feeling like a shooting star
So その瞳にはまってた いつの間にか
So, I was caught in those eyes before I knew it
Because I'm bound to wreck your body and say turn the body out
Say baby what どうしてすれ違って
Say baby, why do we pass each other by
I don't know why ki-ki-kiss のあと
I don't know why, after the kiss
いつの間にか二人は so far apart
Before we knew it, the two of us were so far apart
どうすればいいの baby girl
What should I do, baby girl
A-yo how U feelin' me now
A-yo, how you feeling me now
We should be together and forever
Ah...
隣にいるのに...
Even though you're beside me...
近くにいても boy
Even when you're close, boy
もしかして maybe
Could it be maybe
If you say so...
気が変わる前に trust
Before your mind changes, trust
そして今日もこのまま
And today, just like this
どこまでももう少しだけ
To wherever, just a little bit more
そして朝まで ah, ah, ah, inside
And until morning, ah, ah, ah, inside
隣にいるのに
Even though you're beside me
近くにいても boy
Even when you're close, boy
少しだけ baby
Just a little bit, baby
もしかして maybe
Could it be maybe
If you say so...
気が変わる前に trust
Before your mind changes, trust
そして今日もこのまま
And today, just like this
どこまでももう少しだけ
To wherever, just a little bit more
そして朝まで ah, ah, ah
And until morning, ah, ah, ah
Check it out, 俺たちが m-flow
Check it out, we are m-flow
Rock rock on, we got my girl Melody
Rock rock on, we can't forget Yo-hey
Rock rock on, party people get loud
俺たちが m-flow
We are m-flow
Rock rock on, we got my girl Melody
Rock rock on, we can't forget my man Yo-hey
Rock rock on, party people get loud
Baby... yeah.
Yeah.
Baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby...
It's Going Down Now
Lyrics: Lotus Juice
Music: アトラスサウンドチーム
It's Going Down Now
Lyrics: Lotus Juice
Music: Atlas Sound Team
Yeah, live high, Lotus Juice, one time checking, hey yo.
Distant voices, monsters screaming, what are they thinking? Please explain.
Don't believe this crap and waste some time while I possess coping systems.
Doing it better than just settling for another regular.
Letters to my enemies, yeah, I'm telling them breaking it down to the level molecular.
Alright, better be wise when you're choosing battles, mostly babbles.
You know what are those bits are shady, faux-poses of a binary foe.
Drop these bars in my sleep, few more tricks up my sleeve.
Way too late to choose, believe now!
Disturbing the peace!
Look into my eyes!
Now tell me the things you blabbering about behind my back.
The tenacity!
I hold it tight to break it down.
It's too late for apologies, it's going down now!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Take it away!
You're thirsty for blood as you're craving for love.
What you only want is the greed makes you go numb.
Purposes full of bucket of salt, hey please stop, the talk's about to be of patience.
Because I'm about to knock you out cold.
Bring it back, please.
Whole lot of moves to make you on your life dance.
Blowing doing this beat down, you probably wish that you could fast forward.
Don't you worry about it, leave some room for your last words.
Have to do this, do that, and the third.
Disturbing the peace!
Look into my eyes!
Now tell me the things you blabbering about behind my back.
The tenacity!
I hold it tight to break it down.
It's too late for apologies, it's going down!
And some things may break me.
But I'll always get back up.
New perspective gained from all the pain and stress.
And when I do come back.
I'm stronger than ever before so...
Kneel down! Disturbing the peace!
Look into my eyes!
Now tell me the things you blabbering about behind my back.
The tenacity!
I hold it tight to break it down.
It's too late for apologies, it's going down!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
It's going down now.
That's right, baby.
Thank you so much everyone for listening!
Thank you, thank you.
Oh my gosh, that was so amazing! That was like a dream come true. Oh my gosh!
Thank you so much everyone! If you, if you don't know who this is...
...introduce yourself!
I go by the name of Lotus Juice. Thank you for having me, Calli.
Oh, thank you so much! That was amazing.
That was fun, that was fun.
Oh my gosh! It was seriously a dream of mine though, just because...
Really?
...you know, I mean, I've been a fan of your music like ever since high school, you know?
That's just crazy. I feel old, by the way.
Oh no, not at all! You do not look it at all. You are so awesome. Oh my gosh.
You are too amazing.
I'm fangirling, oh my goodness.
Thank you so much for being here, seriously. Like Persona 3 is one of the things that like made me who I am, I think.
Wow.
And like your, your rap in that game was my first exposure ever to like...
And like your rap in that game was my first exposure ever to like...
...I guess what I would call like J-Rap even though it's in English.
Okay.
So like that was the first time that I heard like a Japanese rapper and thought to myself...
"Oh my God, that's amazing! J-Rap's so cool," you know?
Wow, wow. Appreciate that. I mean, I did it like 18 years ago and...
18 years ago!
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I was a young rapper in Japan trying to make it out there, having fun and...
...it's just crazy that you know, people like you listen to it and now you're the artist and...
...so it's an honor to inspire people like you.
Thank you so much! No, I mean, also J-Rap is like kind of my roots now as well...
...which is why we have this show that's happening right now, you know?
Okay.
This is just incredible, incredible.
Yeah, it's awesome you can join me in this like 3D world.
It's like a transcendental experience.
I love it, man. I love it.
Thank you so much for being here. And also thank you for singing with me on "Sneaking Revenge" as well for my album.
Oh no doubt about that. That was a lot of fun. I mean, it was my first time not writing the lyrics...
...so it's like a cover song, but I met you the first time in the studio and we did it.
Unfortunately had to leave early, but you know, we got to... I got to listen to your recording and you got to listen to mine and it was a lot of fun.
Yeah.
Yeah, just getting to be in the studio together was seriously a dream come true for me. So thank you so much.
And I always thought to myself that I wanted to have like a male vocalist on the track as well...
...and you just fit perfectly because, I don't know, you've got like the coolest voice ever so...
Okay.
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
うわ！やべえ！わー、すごい！ That was awesome. Wow.
Whoa! No way! Wow, incredible! That was awesome. Wow.
I hope that we get a chance to collab again in the future someday on something.
For sure. No doubt, no doubt.
Cool. That would be awesome.
Well sadly we have to say goodbye to Lotus-san for now, but I hope you guys keep enjoying the final song.
The song of the night.
So yes, last song. Please enjoy you guys.
Here's the last song. Enjoy!
Enjoy!
Super Shooter
Lyrics, Music: RIP SLYME
Now listen yo people put your guns up まずは hands up
Now listen yo people put your guns up First, hands up
走り回る奴らを gun shot
Gun shot for those running around
Brand new sound so still survival
Here comes some boy この世界に
Here comes some boy, to this world
軌道 治療 太陽 と 運が舞う the flow
Orbit, treatment, the sun and luck dance in the flow
グランドの真ん中 技プラン何だ
In the middle of the ground, what's the skill plan?
さっぱな出刃にワンパンコンパン
With a sashimi knife, one punch, con punch
ノックカンカンカン
Knock, bang bang bang
One shot for your mind ゆけ look around the world
One shot for your mind, go, look around the world
付きまとうさ いつの人も
It haunts you, anyone, anytime
限界感のまりもも曲がりも
Even the Marimo of the sense of limit and the curve
蒔かれた種も話さなけりゃ黙りの
Even the sown seeds remain silent if you don't speak
生きて打ち込め 地ねの矢を猛猛
Live and drive in the arrows of the earth, fiercely
行き先に明日は言わない
Don't speak of tomorrow at your destination
立ちなさいよ Don't give up the fight
Stand up, don't give up the fight
今そこの瞬間もダイ ダイ ダイ
Even this moment right now, die die die
Big shooter 生き急いで blazing
Big shooter, living fast, blazing
Beat you up 切り開いて break
Beat you up, cut through and break
Shot shooter 生き急いだ crazy
Shot shooter, lived fast, crazy
照準合う 至近距離で break
Aiming, break at close range
Big shooter 生き急いで blazing
Big shooter, living fast, blazing
Beat you up 切り開いて break
Beat you up, cut through and break
Shot shooter 生き急いだ crazy
Shot shooter, lived fast, crazy
照準合う 至近距離で break
Aiming, break at close range
Player 1 start
Link up super gun shooter
a boy can't touch we harness the light up
Freedom 日暮れる前が P.O. please
立て替えのピース
Freedom, before the sun sets P.O. please
payment piece
Swing check 抜きの gun clap
真下で揺らした大地をダンスホール
Swing check, gun clap without
the earth shaken right below is the dance hall
Your body moving 朝まで moving
走行 shooting
Your body moving, moving until morning
running shooting
We got shoot, 攻めるクルー、奴が来るアドバンス取って進む
We got shoot, the attacking crew, he's coming, take the advantage and move forward
X, Z, Z, Crash!
Hey coming up, 神のみぞ知る、犬に印、しっかりリンク、シンとシン
Hey coming up, only God knows, sign the dog, link properly, core to core
一人きり切り開けキラー、生き残るために握るトリガー
Break through on your own, killer, the trigger you pull to survive
セットアップしたフルメトロジャケット
Set up full metro jacket
テンポアップで点々ダダダ、Round 2、新しい世界
Tempo up and dots da-da-da, Round 2, new world
Brand new fantasy, Two-hand shooter
進呈してみせろソレ運動、切り返した出術じっくり動、動、動、変えてない
Show us your gift, that exercise, the switched-back technique moves slowly, move, move, hasn't changed
海千が流れる、白い旗あげても止まらない
A veteran flows, won't stop even if you raise a white flag
De-Point 加算 加速するマザー
De-Point addition, accelerating mother
Can't get any harder, この体 バラバラ
Can't get any harder, this body's in pieces
残れ体、Let's continue まだまだ
Remain body, Let's continue, still more to go
おー、ほらスタート テイクオフ、いつも遠くにパブリックエネミー
Oh, look, start, takeoff, always far away, public enemy
心のモヤ 不安の煙に、負けずまずはファーストブリーズ
Don't lose to the haze in your heart or the smoke of anxiety, first, the first breeze
負けぬ在庫踏まえ、わがままだけのプラン
Based on non-losing stock, a plan of just selfishness
当てもなくに歪んだスリー、飛ばすシンとラン
An aimlessly distorted three, sending the core and the run
サイレン鳴り響く 集まる鳴くデイ
Siren rings out, a gathering, crying day
誰もが待っていきせい 希望 君がヒーロー
Everyone's waiting for high spirits, hope, you're the hero
負けると思うたって 立って、Yo たって立って
Even if you think you'll lose, stand up, stand up, Yo, stand up, stand up
捕らえるロックオン、避けることせず、さぁ体張って
Catch the lock-on, without avoiding, come on, put your body on the line
Yo、さすらいのガンナー、虚空のハンター
Yo, wandering gunner, hunter of the void
Continue、次は誰だ？お前の番だ！
Continue, who's next? It's your turn!
S-O-S、チェック ザ テスト、ボケボケつったってれば速攻ゼン
S-O-S, check the test, if you're just standing around dazed, it's an immediate Zen
ナイスアタック、ナイスディフェンス、必要なのはサバイバルのセンス
Nice attack, nice defense, what's needed is a survival sense
行けろ 行けろ Here we go Here we go、ハイマース、明日はお前がヒーロー
Go, go, Here we go, here we go, High-mers, tomorrow you'll be the hero
Big shooter、生き急いで、Blazing beat you up、切り開いて break
Big shooter, living fast, Blazing beat you up, break through, break
Shot shooter、生き急いで、Crazy 照準合う、至近距離で break
Shot shooter, living fast, Crazy aim's set, at point-blank range, break
Big shooter、生き急いで、Blazing beat you up、切り開いて break
Big shooter, living fast, Blazing beat you up, break through, break
Shot shooter、生き急いで、Crazy 照準合う、至近距離で break
Shot shooter, living fast, Crazy aim's set, at point-blank range, break
Yo, Dead Beats, did you enjoy the show? I've got a couple more announcements for you
before we head off to the MV premiere and then the members-only encore performance
at 9:15 JST. So don't head out yet, okay?
はい、お知らせあります！
Yes, I have announcements!
You know what time it is? Goods time! These are technically to celebrate
my fourth anniversary, but they're themed around today's show.
そうです、グッズあります！
That's right, there's merch!
First off, we've got a poster from the underground. It's a huge poster of me, Mori Calliope,
in Underworld-ian street fashion promoting my J-Rap themed live show.
A nice memory of our night together in Neo-Tokyo.
とっても素敵なポスターです！
It's a very wonderful poster!
Want to write lyrics? Scribble doodles? Write letters to fictional characters
about everyone who bullied you in school? About existential thoughts that plague you daily?
Grab a Mori-themed notebook! It's a super cute design with lots of mini Moraries running around it,
so make it yours today. とっても素敵なノートです！
so make it yours today. It's a very wonderful notebook!
Are you ready to shed your mortal coil and become an actual skeleton?
Well, if you did that, Mori would get in huge trouble, so for now, how about a Dead Beat themed hoodie?
You could also use it as a Halloween costume as a regular old skeleton, but cooler. It's super comfy,
so make sure you grab it. とっても素敵なフーディです！
so make sure you grab it. It's a very wonderful hoodie!
Finally, we have... Oh God. Oh God. No, wait, no, not that thing.
Wait, Mane-chan... Mane-chan, wasn't there something else we were selling? Like a water bottle or something?
Why is this weird freaking cat here? Okay, I'm being told to roll with it.
Uh, Weird Cat is here as a cute plushie for your Mori plushie collection.
Just look, if you buy this thing, be careful, okay? I don't claim any responsibility
for whatever happens to you after. とっても怖いぬいぐるみです！
for whatever happens to you after. It's a very scary plushie!
If you buy all these pieces of merch, you'll get this: a sticker sheet full of mini Moraries.
Stick them onto your car, your computer, your little brother's Switch and see how angry he gets.
I don't know, they're your stickers now, so do whatever you want with them, I guess. 全部のグッズ買ったら、素敵なステッカーもらえます！
I don't know, they're your stickers now, so do whatever you want with them, I guess. If you buy all the goods, you'll get a wonderful sticker!
Now that merch is out of the way, let's talk about my brand new song releasing.
That's right folks, a brand new J-Rap single titled 'FLASH BANG' is coming out right after this stream.
I got to make a song with the J-Rap legend PES-sama, one of the most iconic rappers...
in Japan, a member of RIP SLYME who helped popularize the entire J-Rap genre.
RIP SLYMEのPESさんと一緒にコラボしました！
I've collaborated with PES from RIP SLYME!
やったー！パチパチパチパチ！
Yay! *Clap clap clap clap!*
もうすぐMVリリースしますよ！
The MV will be released soon!
We got a special message from him too, so let's run the clip!
はい。えー、Dead Beatsの皆さん、こんにちは。
Hello, Dead Beats!
PESと申します。どうも。
I'm PES,
えー、Calliopeさんの『Super Shooter』、いかがでしたでございましたでしょうか？
What did you think of Calliope's "Super Shooter"?
えー、この度、私PESがですね、Calliopeさんとコラボさせていただくことになりました。
This time I, PES, had the chance to collaborate with Calliope!
はい、ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much!
私がね、プロデュースさせていただいた、Calliopeさんの新曲『FLASH BANG』がですね、
I was able to produce Calliope's new song, "FLASH BANG",
リリースされることになりました。よいしょー！
which is being released now!
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much!
えー、この曲はですね、あの、まあライブ皆さん楽しみにCalliopeさんのライブ見ていただいてると思うんですけど、
So about this song, I think everyone is really enjoying watching Calliope's Live
そのライブね、こう終わった後だって、いろんな普段の生活の中でもこうパッと、こう連れ戻されるような、
and that Live, once it is over, during your normal everyday life, there are instances
パッと思い出してしまうような、そんな瞬間が彼女のこう魅力の中にあるんじゃないかなっていうことでですね、
where you are just suddenly brought back and just suddenly remember.
パッと、一瞬フッと、その瞬間に戻ってしまえるような、そんな楽しい曲になっておるかと、
Her ability to make people feel that is one of her strong points I feel. Suddenly, in one moment,
思われますので、ぜひ皆さん聴いてみてください。ありがとうございます。
in that instance you remember the song. That fun type of song
is what I think we were able to make,
ぜひ皆さん聴いてみてください。ありがとうございます。
so everyone be sure to listen to it!
ありがとうございます。
Thank you!
Thank you so much, PES-san! Another one of my big dreams has come true.
I hope you guys loop the song lots and enjoy the super cute animated music video.
It really encapsulates my love for Japanese rap, and I hope those feelings come through to all of you when you listen.
Thanks again for tuning in, everyone! Keep enjoying J-Rap.
Keep enjoying Mori. Keep enjoying things that make you happy.
Catch you on the flip side, and hopefully at the premiere and member's encore. Peace!